This protocol performs an interface design and minimization on chain B of a binary complex using three design steps:
First, an aggressive step explores large areas of sequence space using scorefunctions with very low repulsive penalties
Second, a soft step smoothes in the rough edges by designing with a soft scorefunction, but minimizing with a standard one
Finally, a cleanup step pulls everything together with a standard scorefunction and minimizes over all degrees of freedom (rigid body, sidechain, and backbone)

Note that this protocol only operates over the first jump. Binary complexes are fine, but ternary+ complexes will only design partner2.
<dock_design>
        <SCOREFXNS>
        </SCOREFXNS>
        <FILTERS>
                <Sasa name=sasa confidence=0/> change confidence to 1, if you want low-sasa structures to be suppressed.
                <Ddg name=ddg confidence=0/>
        </FILTERS>
        <MOVERS>
                <RepackMinimize name=des_explore scorefxn_repack=score_docking scorefxn_minimize=soft_rep minimize_bb=0/> Exploration: Design and minimization with very soft repulsive potentials. Rigid body and sidechains are minimized (default true). No backbone minimization.
                <RepackMinimize name=des_smooth scorefxn_repack=soft_rep scorefxn_minimize=score12 minimize_bb=0/> Smoothing: Design with a soft potential, minimization with a normal potential. No backbone minimization.
                <RepackMinimize name=des_clean scorefxn_repack=score12 scorefxn_minimize=score12/> Cleanup. Design and minimization with a normal potential. Backbone is minimized (backbone minimization with anything other than score12 is NOT recommended!)
		<DockDesign name=design> Packages all three design movers into one easy-to-call combo. Movers are called in the order they are specified.
			<Add mover_name=des_explore/>
			<Add mover_name=des_smooth/>
			<Add mover_name=des_clean/>
		</DockDesign>
        </MOVERS>
        <APPLY_TO_POSE>
        </APPLY_TO_POSE>
        <PROTOCOLS>
		<Add mover_name=design/>
		<Add filter_name=ddg/>
		<Add filter_name=sasa/>
        </PROTOCOLS>
</dock_design>
