<ROSETTASCRIPTS>
    <SCOREFXNS>
	<ScoreFunction name="score_dock_low" weights="interchain_cen" />
    </SCOREFXNS>
    <FILTERS>
    </FILTERS>
    <MOVERS>
	// the move
	<SwitchResidueTypeSetMover name="switch2centroid" set="centroid"/>	// sampling in low resolution
	<ThermodynamicRigidBodyPerturbNoCenter name="rb_mover" rot_mag="1" trans_mag="0.5"/> // unbiased mover for translation and rotation, mover step size using constant gaussian mean value, alternatively use dock_cen_inter.xml, which interpolate mover's step size based on temperature level

	// setup jumps and constraints
	<DockSetupMover name="setup_jump"/> // setup fold_tree, and store movable_jump into RigidBodyInfo
	<AddEncounterConstraintMover name="encounter_cst" gap="8" />  // very loose Atompair constraint between closest-to-mass-center CAs. For example: "AtomPair  CA   337  CA   531 BOUNDED       0.1 s(1)+s(2)+gap 0.5 Encounter" , 337 and 531 are the closest-to-mass-center residues of each docking partners respectively, and s(i) is the furthest distance of a surface CA of docking partner i to its center CA.
	<DockingInitialPerturbation name="init_pert" randomize2="1" randomize1="1" />	// randomly reorient the two docking partners, actually this does not matter in ReplicaDock sampling low-resolution because ReplicaDock forgets its initial position very fast.
	// sampling engine
        <TrialCounterObserver name="count" file="trial.stats"/> // acceptance rate recorder
        <HamiltonianExchange name="h_exchange" temp_file="hamiltonians_cen.txt"  temp_stride="1000"/> // temp_file contains the temperature configuration. exchange between neighbor temperature is attempted every 1000 strides. No specific reason why using HamiltonianExchange mover intead of ParalleTempering, only because I started with it at the very beginning and it works as well if only temperature exchange involved.
	<SilentTrajectoryRecorder name="traj" score_stride="1" stride="1000" cumulate_replicas="1" /> // take snapshots every 1000 stride and output the decoy into a trajectory silent file
	<MetropolisHastings name="sampler" trials="2000" scorefxn="score_dock_low" > // normally use trials=5000000. Empirically, it is enough for converge. Here 5000 is only for example_runs. 
	    <Add mover_name="h_exchange"/>
	    <Add mover_name="traj"/>
	    <Add mover_name="count"/>
	    <Add mover_name="rb_mover"/>
	</MetropolisHastings>

    </MOVERS>
    <APPLY_TO_POSE>
    </APPLY_TO_POSE>
    <PROTOCOLS>
	<Add mover_name="switch2centroid"/>
	<Add mover_name="setup_jump"/>
	<Add mover_name="encounter_cst"/>
	<Add mover_name="init_pert"/>
	<Add mover_name="sampler"/>
    </PROTOCOLS>


</ROSETTASCRIPTS>
