Scan all interface residues on chain B (designed chain) and report all substitutions that do not 
destabilize the monomer (in the unbound state) as well as do not reduce binding affinity or add strain. 
Use bb/rb/sc minimization before evaluating these energetic parameters.

Run this script on input structures that have been prepacked with bb minimization on chain B. 
It is crucial to have a proper reference state for all of the energetic calculations here!

More generally, this script can be used to scan across a set of residues with a filter. 
It will create a detailed list of the consequences of mutations in each allowed position 
as well as output a resfile containing all allowable residues according to the filter. 
After each mutation a user-defined relax mover is called.

Potential uses: scan all positions in a set of scaffolds to identify mutations that won't 
destabilize the protein too much; residue scans (ala, trp, etc.) on a large set of proteins.

Running: rosetta_scripts -database  -s  -parser:protocol  -ex1 -ex2 -include_input_sc

Run each input file in a separate directory to ensure that the resfiles that are output 
do not override one another.

<dock_design>
	<SCOREFXNS>
		<sc12 weights=score12_full />
		<sc12_w_PB weights=score12_full patch=pb_elec/>
		<soft_rep weights=soft_rep />
	</SCOREFXNS>
	<TASKOPERATIONS>
		<InitializeFromCommandline name=init/>
		<ProteinInterfaceDesign name=pido allow_all_aas=1 design_all_aas=1 interface_distance_cutoff=14.0/>
		<ProteinInterfaceDesign name=repack_interface design_chain1=0 design_chain2=0/>
		The two resfiles below will be written out as intermediate files by the ScanFilter functions, below.
		<ReadResfile name=binding_mutations filename="binding.resfile"/>
		Histidines are a source of trouble for Rosetta energetics at the interface. Better to avoid them completely
		<RestrictAbsentCanonicalAAS name=nohis keep_aas="ACDEFGIKLMNPQRSTVWY"/> 
	</TASKOPERATIONS>
	<MOVERS>
		<SetupPoissonBoltzmannPotential name=setup_pb scorefxn=sc12_w_PB charged_chains=1 epsilon=2.0 apbs_path="/home/honda/dvlp/rosetta-trunk/rosetta_source/external/apbs/apbs-1.4-rosetta/bin/apbs" apbs_debug=3 calcenergy=0/>
		connect chains by their geometric centres. Good for minimization
		<AtomTree name=docking_tree docking_ft=1/> 
		minimize sc, rb, and bb (of chain 2 only)
                <MinMover name=min_all jump=1 bb=0 chi=1> 
                        <MoveMap>
                                <Chain number=1 bb=0 chi=1/>
                                <Chain number=2 bb=1 chi=1/>
                        </MoveMap>
                </MinMover>
		<PackRotamersMover name=pack_interface_soft scorefxn=soft_rep task_operations=init,repack_interface/>
		<PackRotamersMover name=pack_interface scorefxn=sc12  task_operations=init,repack_interface/>
		before running the baseline calculation in filter scan, you need to relax the ppk'ed structure
		<ParsedProtocol name=relax_before_baseline> 
			<Add mover=docking_tree/>
                        <Add mover=pack_interface_soft/>
                        <Add mover=min_all/>
                        <Add mover=pack_interface/>
                        <Add mover=min_all/>
                        <Add mover=pack_interface/>
                        <Add mover=min_all/>
		</ParsedProtocol>
		<SavePoseMover name=save_pose_after_pb_setup reference_name=pose_after_pb_setup/>
	</MOVERS>

	<FILTERS>
		I think that 1 repeat should suffice as the calculations on minimized designs are actually rather stable.
		<Ddg name=ddg scorefxn=sc12_w_PB confidence=0.0 repeats=2 translate_by=100/> 
		Here, measuring the binding energy gain
		<Delta name=delta_ddg filter=ddg upper=1 lower=0 range=-0.5 relax_mover=relax_before_baseline reference_name=pose_after_pb_setup/> 
		produces a resfile showing shiwch subset of the non-destabilizing mutations (from the above step) do not harm binding affinity
		<FilterScan name=scan_binding scorefxn=sc12_w_PB relax_mover=relax_before_baseline task_operations=pido,init,nohis filter=delta_ddg triage_filter=delta_ddg resfile_name="binding.resfile"/> 
		<Time name=scan_binding_timer/>
	</FILTERS>
	<PROTOCOLS>
                <Add mover=setup_pb/>
		<Add mover=save_pose_after_pb_setup/>
		<Add mover=docking_tree/>
		<Add filter=scan_binding_timer/>
		<Add filter=ddg/>
		Add filter=scan_binding/> slowest (two repacks x repeats)
		<Add filter=scan_binding_timer/>
	</PROTOCOLS>
</dock_design>
